I feel it stirrin' deep down inside my soul
有一种悸动在我灵魂中回响
The rhythm's takin' hold
是节拍在生长
And it's about to roll
即将翻腾跌宕
A million sparkles falling across the floor
万千星光都散落在地上
So DJ give it more
DJ继续疯狂
It's what we're looking for
我们闪亮登场
Dance the night away
舞动一整夜
All our friends right by our side
朋友齐聚在舞台
It doesn't matter what style you bring
所有的风格都不见外
We're about to go on that ride
让我们一起秀出来
It's dance magic
热舞魔法
Once you have it
去感受它
Let your body move, step into the music
随心而动 紧跟音乐步伐
It's dance magic
热舞魔法
And it's electric
能量爆炸
Let your body move to the music
自由踩上音乐的步伐
Doesn't matter what style you've got
无论你风格怎么样
Just keep dancin' on that spot
忘我热舞最奔放
Your friends like you for who you are
朋友喝彩声势壮
Dance queen,on the scene,superstar!
舞姿就属你最靓
Crystal Prep, you've got the moves
水晶预科动作酷
Rainboom bringin' all the grooves
虹爆秀出新舞姿
Put it together and make it fit
融会贯通再成一家
Crystal Rainbooms, dance magic
水晶虹爆 热舞魔法
Dance the night away
舞动一整夜
All our friends right by our side
朋友齐聚在舞台
It doesn't matter what style you bring
所有的风格都不见外
We're about to go on that ride
我们在此刻秀出来
It's dance magic
热舞魔法
Once you have it
去感受它
Let your body move
随心而动
Step into the music
紧跟音乐步伐
It's dance magic
热舞魔法
And it's electric
能量爆炸
Let your body move to the music
自由踩上音乐的步伐
Crystal Rainbooms got a style that's all our own
水晶和虹爆都有自己的舞蹈
Dancin' nonstop, body movin' in the zone
身姿曼妙 跟上音乐不停脚
Bring whatever style you've got
各种风格一起跳
'Cause the party is goin' off
因为派对已经燃烧
It's dance magic
热舞魔法
And it's electric
能量爆炸
Let your body move to the music
自由踩上音乐的步伐